（走过的路）
- 到底是谁 - 利维坦
- Who the hell! - Leviathan!
离我远点
Stay the hell away from me.
你的世界由我主宰 明白了吗
Your world is whatever I want it to be, understand?
离我远一点
Leave me alone!
你想知道真相吗 你出来了
You want to know the truth? You got away.
我们把你弄出来了 小萨姆 这是真实的
We got you out, Sammy. This is real.
你们得去见一个名叫弗兰克·德弗罗的家伙
You need to see a fella named Frank Devereaux.
是鲍比·辛格派我们来的
Bobby singer sent us.
你们对我们造不成威胁 我们有不死之身
You can't stop any of us. We can't be killed.
那些家伙比你们狡猾多了
These things are smarter than you.
你们根本不知道怎么杀它们
You don't have a clue how to kill 'em.
或是拖延时间 而你们的计划是什么
or slow 'em down, and your plan is, what?
- 正面交锋吗 - 孩儿们好
- Go right at 'em? - Hello, boys.
多年追杀你的恶魔
Years of demons nipping at your heels,
却已经几个月没见到了 想知道原因吗
haven't seen one for months. Wonder why?
我们忙着呢
We've been busy.
忙着猎杀利维坦 我知道
Hunting Leviathan … yes, I know.
你们见过那个迪克（混蛋）了吗
You met that dick yet?
我们应当成为朋友 我和你
We should be friends, you and I.
我永远不会跟你合作 克劳力
I'd never work with you, Crowley.
好吧 狗娘养的 看看你们到底想干嘛
Okay, you sons of bitches. Let's see what you're up to.
快走
Go! Go!
赶紧呼叫待命的神经外科医生
Page the neurosurgeon on call.
他不会死 只是一枚子弹而已
He's not gonna die. It's one bullet.
他不会有事 因为他向来如此
He's gonna be fine because he's always fine.
也许我不是真实存在的
So maybe I'm not real,
但我哪里也不去 萨姆
but I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
他睁眼了
His eyes are open.
鲍比
Bobby?
小混球
Idjits.
鲍比
Bobby?
（如今）
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
你已经连续在这儿待了好几晚了
You've been here a couple nights in a row now.
谁让我喜欢这里的氛围呢
What can I say? I like the ambience.
还需要点别的吗
Get you anything else?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
谢谢 路上注意安全
Thanks. Keep safe out there.
你好啊 迷路了吗
Hey, there. You lost?
什么
What?
不好意思
Excuse me…
你看上去有点精神恍惚哦
You're looking a little cabo wabo, there.
不 我没事
No. No, I'm fine.
怎么可能没事
No. You're not.
你忙着欣赏窗外小妞的时候
I slipped a little special sauce into your coffee.
我在你的咖啡里加了点儿特殊作料
while you were watching the skirt.
你知道我们能分泌毒液吧
You do know we're venomous, right?
看来给你下药的剂量还不够足
Looks like I didn't dose you quite hard enough.
没关系
That's okay.
毒液要多少有多少
There's more where that came from.
小费给那么少 给你点儿教训
That's for the crappy tip.
[邪恶力量 第7季第11集]
（第一周）
（第二周）
（邮政编码）
（第三周）
（比格森餐厅召回被污染肉类 顾客食用火鸡鸭三明治后染病）
迪恩 跟你说
Dean, you know, um…
我在想 我们是不是…
…I wonder if … if we…
应该向大家公布这个消息
I mean, should we be telling people?
我是指认识他的人
I mean, people he knew.
我把那组数字给弗兰克多久了
How long ago did I give Frank these numbers?
好几周了 对吧
It's been a few weeks, right?
他是解不出来 还是懒得联系咱们
What, is he nuts, or is he just being rude?
大概两者都有吧
Probably both.
迪恩 我得问你个问题
Dean, I-I got to ask you a question.
除非他遭遇了不测
Unless, of course, something happened to him.
脸被利维坦咬掉了 所以没法打电话
He can't get to the phone because a Leviathan ate his face.
也有这种可能
Yeah, also a possibility.
我们该去一探究竟
We should go check on him.
迪恩 你到底想不想打电话通知鲍比的朋友
Dean, do you want to call Bobby's people or not?
为什么要我们来通知
W-why is that our job?
不然还有谁来做
Because who else is gonna do it?
我不想给任何人打电话
I'm not calling anybody.
你要是想打 自己打去
If you want to, you go right ahead.
我也不想打电话 开什么玩笑
I don't want to call anybody. You kidding me?
我可不接
Well, I'm not getting it.
喂
Hello?
鲍比·辛格在吗
Is Bobby Singer there?
不在 他…
Uh, no. He's, uh…
我不是…我是他朋友
I-I-it's not, but I'm a friend of his.
我爸特别交代要我找鲍比·辛格本人
My Dad asked me to call Bobby Singer specifically.
他不在 但如果你需要…
He's…not here, but, look, if you need s…
谁打来的
Who was it?
一个孩子
Just some kid.
找鲍比吗
For Bobby?
卖饼干的女童子军
Girl scout cookies?
我觉得可能是
I think maybe…
可能是个猎人的孩子
Maybe a-a hunter's kid?
她听上去很害怕
I mean, she sounded pretty scared.
这里有来电号码 我们该去找她
You know, I have a caller I.D. Maybe we should go find her.
看看她有没有危险
We can check on her.
那弗兰克怎么办
What about Frank?
迪恩 我觉得我们应该先去找这个女孩
Well, Dean, I think we should go find this girl first.
萨姆 弗兰克正在破解
Sam, Frank's been working on the numbers.
鲍比用最后一口气写下的数字
that Bobby spent his last breath on,
这事你也要往后推吗
And you want to back-burner that?
好吧 你去找那个女童子军
Fine. You go check out girl scout.
我去找弗兰克
I'll find Frank.
好吧 但我有个条件
Fine. But you know what? On one condition …
如果你发现弗兰克还活得好好的
If Frank is just spinning his wheels,
那你就撇下那个疯子 赶紧来找我
then you bail out on crazy and come meet me.
你把我的啤酒喝光了 十分感谢
And thanks for drinking my entire beer.
我没碰你的啤酒 我的在那
I didn't touch your beer. Mine's right there.
八成是你不知不觉喝光的
You probably drank it without noticing.
好吧
Right.
你好
Hello?
我们之前通过电话
Um, we…spoke on the phone earlier?
你好
Hi.
我是萨姆
Uh…I'm sam.
你在电话里听上去需要帮助
You sounded like you needed help,
我正好在这附近
and I was in the area.
你是怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
鲍比的通讯簿里有你爸的地址
Your dad is in Bobby's address book.
那他人呢
So where is he?
鲍比吗
Bobby?
他去世了
He's passed away.
听我说
Look, um …
- 克里希 - 克里希
- Krissy. - Krissy.
我明白 不能让陌生人进门
I get it. You don't let strangers in.
不过如果你爸爸说可以相信鲍比
But if your dad said you could trust Bobby,
你也可以相信我
then you can trust me, too.
听清楚 911设了快捷拨号
Just so you know, 911's on speed-dial.
一键搞定
One button.
当然 记住了
Yeah, sure. Note taken.
这么说
So…
你也是推销员
…you're a salesman, too?
是
Yep.
你爸爸还在外面没回来
So your dad's on the road right now?
有一阵子了吧
Been gone a while?
他以前每晚都会打电话来
He usually calls every night.
多久没联系你了
How long has it been?
五天
Five days.
家里只有你和他吗
It's just you and him, huh?
我知道这种感觉
I know how that is.
听着
Look, um…
干我们这一行 总有个马高蹬短
Sometimes on the road, crap happens.
我会帮你找到他
So I'll help you track him down.
- 真的吗 - 当然
- Really? - 'course.
他有没有说他去哪儿了
Did he happen to say where he was going?
他说在道奇城附近有几个客户
Said he had a couple leads near Dodge City.
他有没有书桌什么的
And does he have a desk or something.
存放他的东西
where he keeps his stuff?
你能给我煮杯咖啡吗
Do you mind making some coffee?
谢谢
Thanks.
（失踪报告 堪萨斯州立警察局）
克里希
Krissy.
是这样的 我知道去哪里调查了
Hey, listen, so I think I got an idea where to start.
所以这就走了
So I'm gonna go.
这个能借给我用吗
Um…can I borrow this?
好
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有
Here.
这有一个号码
Here's a number,
如果几天后没有我的消息 就打过去
in case you don't hear from me in the next couple days.
别担心
Don't worry.
我保证会打电话来报平安
I promise I'll check in.
别这样说 我爸爸也是这样说的
Don't say that. That's what my dad said.
情况不妙啊
This can't be good.
你好啊
Well…hi.
弗兰克
Frank…
我们可是朋友
We're amongst friends here.
好吧 熟人
Okay, acquaintances.
利维坦肯定也会这样说
That's just what a Leviathan would say.
弗兰克 我不是利维坦
Frank…I'm not a Leviathan.
当然了 你不是利维坦
Oh, sure. You're not a Leviathan.
迪克·罗曼不是利维坦
Dick Roman's not a Leviathan.
格温妮丝·帕特洛（著名演员）也不是利维坦
Gwyneth Paltrow is not a Leviathan.
真的吗
Yeah?
相信我
Trust me.
好吧 听我说 弗兰克
Okay. You know what, Frank?
你调查得有点过头了吧
I think you've been doing a little too much research.
他们无处不在 千变万化
They're anywhere, anyone.
老弗兰克知道的太多了
Who's to say this ain't the day.
谁知道他们今天会不会来下毒手
they come for old Frank who knew too much?
他们的血是黑色胶状物 对吧
They bleed black goo, right?
要不要看看我的血是什么样的
You want to see what I bleed?
我们都别动枪 行不行
Let's take the guns out of it, okay?
行
Okay.
看到没 正宗的红血美国人
See? Red-blooded American.
好了
Now…
该你了
Your turn.
算了吧 我显然不是…
Oh! Whoa. Look, I'm obviously not …
要讲公平 混蛋
Fair's fair, douchebag.
好吧
Yeah.
很高兴我们俩一起见红
I'm glad we could share that together.
拿好枪 跟我来
Grab your gun, come with me.
千万不要弄出什么声响
For god's sake, don't make any noise.
怎么缩小规模了
Why the downsize?
还不是因为你
You!
弗兰克 好好查查理查德·罗曼
"Hey, Frank, go dig up some dirt on Richard Roman."
那天晚上 我所有的IP都用报废了
That night, I was burned off every I.P. I had.
电话有人监听 房子受到监控
Ears on my phones, eyes on my house…
等等 是迪克派人监视你吗
Wait … Dick's got people watching you?
我怎么知道
Do I look like I know?
你以为就我这妄想症的程度
You think it's easy to see this deep into what's real.
去深入挖掘真相容易吗
and also be bipolar with delusional ideation?
我的情况无药可救了 小宝贝
There is no pill for my situation, sweetiepop,
所以最靠谱的猜测是 大嘴怪冲着我来了
so, yeah, best guess … the bigmouths are onto me.
还有什么问题
Next question.
好吧 关于大嘴怪有什么消息
All right. Well, what's the word on the bigmouths?
他们的触手无所不及
Their tentacles are everywhere.
我看到了银行家
I-I'm looking at bankers,
军方高层
Military high-ups…
所以你没有回我的电话
This is why you didn't call me back.
你就饶了我吧
Hey, cut me some slack.
你是四天前给我打的电话
You called me like four days ago.
是四个星期以前 弗兰克
I called you four weeks ago, Frank.
什么 乱讲
What? No.
真的吗
Really?
管它几天 你就别逼我了
Days, weeks … quit busting my chops.
什么 你逗我玩吗
What, are you kidding me?
你给我冷静点 娃儿
You cool your heels, buster brown.
弗兰克 我可付了你一万五
Frank, I paid you 15 grand for this.
- 是 我懂 - 不 你根本不懂
- Yeah, I get that… - No, you don't get that!
我就只有迪克·罗曼这一张牌
Dick Roman is every card in my hit deck.
懂不懂
You understand that?
那些数字肯定跟他有什么关联 明白吗
Those numbers, they got something to do with him, okay?
鲍比就是为此而死的
Bobby died for those numbers.
听着 我对鲍比的事感到遗憾
Look, I'm sorry about Bobby.
真心话
I really am.
你也知道 那次在夫勒斯诺市
You know, this one time, we were in Fresno,
当时我们困住了…
and we got stuck …
别说了 别说了
No. No, no, no.
我才不听你这套
I'm not gonna play.
那次我和鲍比怎么怎么的把戏
"this one time with Bobby" Crap, all right?
你根本就不怎么认识他
I'm not gonna get all warm and fuzzy.
少来跟我搞温情
with somebody else who barely knew him.
我只是想说点友好的话
Just trying to make friendly conversation.
我们没什么可友好的 我付了钱 弗兰克
This is not a friendship, Frank. I'm paying you!
听着 你知道你需要什么吗
Hey. You know what you need?
来点迷幻药
A little LSD,
- 再做个按摩 - 我走了
- a little shiatsu… - I'm out of here.
你想不想知道那组数字的含义了
Hey, you want to know what those numbers are?
啥都不是
Bupkes.
不是彩票号码 不是车牌
They're not lottery numbers, license …
这我知道 弗兰克 多谢指教
I know that, Frank. Thank you.
这样一来 我们就只能依靠概率了
Which leaves us little else to do but probability generate.
你说什么
Come again?
你去查一个要死的酒鬼写的
You run most reasonable possibilities.
跟利维坦有关的五位数码
for a Levi-related five-digit number.
可能是什么意思 却毫无结果
written by a dying drunk, you come up flat.
你知道你想到了什么吗
Know what you start to wonder?
「说不定少了一个数」
"Hey, maybe I'm missing a number."
你怎么想到的
Well, how you figure.
不知道啊
Oh, I don't know.
因为鲍比当时颅脑损伤就要死了
Because Bobby was dying of brain trauma.
我想我们什么都查不到是有原因的
I just had a tickle there's a reason nothing was popping out at us,
所以我编了个程序 匹配可能的六位数码
So I set up a program to run possibilities for six numbers,
还有七位和八位
seven, eight.
- 但好消息是 - 有好消息
- But good news. - Good news.
六位就查到了 因为这些数字
Never had to go past six, because this…
我的小羊羔 是坐标
…my little lamb, is coordinates.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
指向哪里
To what?
威斯康星洲的一片野地
A field in Wisconsin.
不
No.
不对 鲍比才不会给我们一个
No, Bobby didn't give us coordinates.
智兹维尔一片杂草地的坐标呢
to some patch of weeds in cheeseville.
不 他给你的坐标指向的地皮
No, he gave you coordinates to a parcel.
刚刚被威廉公司收购
recently purchased by Willman, Inc.,
而这家公司正是…
a subsidiary of…
理查德·罗曼企业旗下的子公司
…Richard Roman enterprises.
那我们怎么办
So what do we do?
躲远点
Stay away.
或者 如果我们很傻
Or, if we're stupid…
就跑过去设立监控设备
we go there and set up surveillance.
马修·海夫莱纳
Matthew Havlena …
在州际公路的地沟里找到的
found in a ditch off the interstate.
死因是什么
Cause of death?
失血五品脱肯定是原因之一
Missing five pints of blood can't have helped.
还有穿刺伤
Puncture wounds …
股动脉和颈动脉都有
femoral arteries and carotid.
那么是动物袭击吗
So, what? Some kind of animal attack?
也可能是吸血鬼
Or a vampire.
别人一般至少会笑笑
Huh. That…usually gets at least a chuckle.
找到弗兰克了吗
Find Frank?
找到了 那些数字是坐标
Yeah. Those numbers? Coordinates.
迪克买了块地 我们正往那边去
Dick bought some land. We're headed there now.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
- 你们就那么开车过去…-别紧张
- You're just gonna drive right up to… - Relax.
一片空地而已 又不是闯死星
It's a field, not the Death Star.
迪克去参加TED大会了
Dick's at a T.E.D. conference.
《哈芬顿邮报》上都写着呢
It's all over the Huffington Post.
慢着
Wait, wait, wait.
你什么时候开始看报了
Since when do you read?
知己知彼 萨姆
Know your enemy, Sam.
女孩的事怎么样了
What's going on with the girl?
我觉得她都不知道她爸爸是个猎人
I don't think she even knows her Dad's in the life.
目前 有三个卡车司机失踪
So far, I got three missing truckers.
还有一具血被吸干的尸体
and one blood-free body.
好世道啊
Good times.
好了 有情况告诉我
All right, well, keep me posted.
设备都弄好了
Got the equipment arranged.
过来穿上服装 我们快点动身
Come and get your costume on. We can scoot.
还「服装」
"Costume"?
搞毛啊
What?
这里有什么特别的
What the hell's so special abou this place?
我最喜欢谜题了
I love a mystery.
快坐吊车台上去
Now get up in that cherry picker.
装成维修东西的样子
and act like you're fixing something.
我不知道怎么用那东西
I don't know how to drive that thing.
你以为我知道
You think I do?
凭什么我要去干…
Well, why do I got to be the sap that …
这件上写着「经理」 这件写着「技工」
This one says "manager." That one says "technician."
这个月内能上去不
Sometime this month?
擦
Crap!
下来吧 泰山
Come on down, Tarzan!
- 干什么 - 快下来
- What?! - Get down here.
我们得走了
We need to move.
这地方他们安了一堆摄像头
They got this place wired up the wazoo.
他们现在就能看到我们吗
They're watching us right now?
他们只是看到了电话公司的张三李四
Nah, nah, they're just watching Cheech and Ed from Ma Bell.
要知道 如果这里到处是监控设备
You know, it's gonna be a little difficult.
我们还想再安监控设备
to set up surveillance if there's,
可是有点难啊
uh, surveillance everywhere.
没错 所以我们改用切入他们的设备
Right. So we need to tap into theirs instead.
好了 现在干什么
All right, now what?
你气色真差
You look horrific.
你上次好好睡一觉是什么时候的事了
When was the last time you really slept a night?
我们赶紧干活 成不
Let's just work, all right?
这就是干活儿了
This is it.
我们盯着屏幕
We watch the screens.
我先值第一班岗
I can take the first shift.
你要是想帮忙…
You're no use if you can't even…
也要睁得开眼才行
keep your eyes open.
迪恩
Dean, hey.
我觉得这个人在猎杀一个嗜血鬼
So I think this guy was hunting a Vetala.
爸爸以前干掉过一个
Dad took one down back in the day.
银质刀子刺入心脏 扭一下 就行了
Silver knife to the heart, twist, they're done.
他写到他们大多离群索居
He says they're maladjusted loner types …
喜欢把人打晕 拖回去 慢慢享用
like to knock a guy out, drag him home, feed slow.
所以说 如果克里希的爸爸被抓走了
So, if Krissy's dad got grabbed,
他或许还活着
there's a chance he might still be alive.
真想把这女孩的父亲送回家
It'd be nice to get this girl's dad back home to her, you know?
好了 你能帮我就好了
All right, I could use your help.
给我回电话
Call me.
打扰
Excuse me.
你们经理说你或许能帮上我
Your manager said that you might be able to help me.
没问题 有什么事
Sure. What can I do for you?
你见过这个人吗
You ever see this man?
前两天可能招待过他
I…might have served him the other day.
我觉得他可能是去…
I think he may have gone to…
找外边那个女孩了
talk to that girl out there.
多谢
Thanks.
能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a second, uh…
萨莉
Sally?
你见过这个男人吗
You ever see this man?
没有
No.
你确定
You sure?
这里不安全
It's not safe here.
咱们找地方私下聊
Somewhere private.
这里不太平
Something's happening around here.
我怕下一个会是我
I'm afraid I'll be next.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you saw.
我不知道我看到了什么
I don't know what I saw.
萨莉 快跑
Sally, run!
我睡了多久
How long was I out?
大约36小时
'bout 36 hours.
什么
What?
你怎么不叫醒我
Why didn't you wake me?
我又不是你管家
Not your butler.
来看这个
Come see this.
什么
What?
这才是高潮
This is where it gets good.
弗兰克 别一副宅男样
Frank, you need to get out more.
不是那个意思
Not that.
瞧瞧这位女强人
Check out Sarah Palin.
她是谁
Who is she?
阿曼达·威勒
Amanda Willer.
想不到吧
Surprise, surprise …
她在理查德·罗曼手下工作
works for Richard Roman.
她在这里做什么
What was she doing?
做个娇蛮的小淘气
Being a naughty, bossy little girl.
抱歉我想听不带色情意味的版本
Well, I hate to ask for that in the non-porno version.
他们在做调查
They're surveying.
他们正准备建个什么东西
They're getting ready to build something.
- 要建什么 - 问得好
- Build what? - Exactly.
建什么
"What?"
毫无头绪
No idea.
我们要怎么搞清楚
Well, how do we find out?
我们继续观察
We watch.
耐心点 小蟋蟀
Patience, grasshopper.
我和耐心一向不合拍
Yeah, patience and me aren't exactly on terms.
那就出门大开杀戒
Well, then go out and kill something.
或者做点你们平时用来消火的事
or whatever you kids do to blow off steam.
怎么 不喜欢我的建议
What, you don't like my suggestion?
我觉得你没资格给我建议 成不
I don't think you're in a position to be giving suggestions, all right?
你带个锡纸帽就能进精神病院了
I think you're one tinfoil hat away from a rubber room.
我告诉你你气色很差了吗
Did I mention you look awful?
说了
Yes.
也许是因为我在乎的一个人
Maybe because somebody I cared about.
刚被爆头而死
just got shot in the head.
这事就是徒劳一场
And this is like shoving a rock up a hill.
还有 去死吧
And … screw you.
我不请自说地给你个建议 放弃吧
Here's my advice you didn't ask for … quit.
什么
What?!
你想继续下去吗
You want to keep going?
我想迪克·罗曼去死
I want Dick Roman on a spit.
但你这幅德行 肯定先把自己累死
But you're gonna drive yourself into the ground first.
真是好主意
Good plan.
我不会放弃的
I'm not gonna quit.
绝不可能
It's not even an option.
我不会抛下我弟弟不管
I'm not gonna walk out on my brother.
那好吧 那就像我一样做
Okay, then, fine. Do what I did.
什么 藏头露尾吗
What? Go native?
囤积C型口粮（美国陆军口粮）
Stock up on C-Rations?
错 小可爱
No, cupcake.
我指的是我26岁那年
What I did when I was 26.
回家发现我妻子和两个孩子
and came home to find my wife and two kids.
被人开膛破肚之后做的事
gutted on the floor.
强迫自己到周末的时候就要打起精神来
Decide to be fine till the end of the week.
只要活着就要保持微笑
Make yourself smile because you're alive.
这就是你该做的
and that's your job.
下一周继续如此
Then do it again the next week.
我要假装若无其事
So fake it?
我管这叫职业素养
I call it being professional.
要么面带微笑 好好干
Do it right, with a smile,
要么直接退出
or don't do it.
迪恩
Dean, hey.
我觉得这个人在猎杀一个嗜血鬼
So I think this guy was hunting a Vetala.
爸爸以前干掉过一个
Dad took one down back in the day.
不不不 萨姆 这可不对
No, no, no. Sam, that's not right.
怎么了
What's the guff?
他写到他们属于离群索居型的
…says they're maladjusted loner types …
喜欢把人打晕 拖回去 慢慢享用
like to knock a guy out, drag him home …
萨姆
Sam.
不是 你是谁
No. Who's this?
你又是谁
Who's this?
萨姆叮嘱我
Sam told me to call.
如果他没音讯的话就打电话给你
if I didn't hear anything back from him.
你的耳鸣
That ringing in your ears …
是毒液造成的
It's from the venom.
毒液
Venom?
是的
Yeah.
他们给你注射了某种迷药
They hit you with some kind of knockout juice.
你看起来挺冷静的
You seem to be handling this pretty well.
是啊
Yeah. Well, um…
我是来找你的
I was out there looking for you.
你是李·钱伯斯
Lee Chambers?
我是鲍比·辛格的朋友
I'm a friend of Nobby Singer's.
克里希给我打了电话
Krissy called.
她 她没事
She … she's fine.
她 她只是很担心你
She is. She's just worried about you.
我们如何逃离这里
So how do we get out of here?
它们很快就会回来
They'll be back pretty quick here.
只有两个吗
Just the two of them?
是的 一对儿搭档
Yeah, they're a tag team.
一个把你迷昏
One of them knocks you out.
另一个把你的卡车 轿车或是什么的
The other one dumps your rig or your ride or whatever.
丢在几英里外的路上
miles down the road.
它们这一套玩得很溜
It's a pretty nice system they got.
它们吸你的血
They've been draining you.
是的
Yeah.
吸个三四次 你就血尽人亡了
They tap you three, four times, you're dead.
让我告诉你
And let me tell you.
你看不见
You can't see…
走不动
You can't walk.
我以为它们当场就会杀死我
I thought they'd kill me right off,
但它们无需这样做
but they don't have to.
他们根本不必担心
They got nothing to worry about.
它们吸了你几次血
How many times they fed on you?
三次
Three.
萨姆告诉你他要去哪里了吗
Did Sam tell you where he was going?
我也想弄清楚
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
你跟他说什么了
What did you tell him?
他检查了我爸爸的房间
Uh…he checked my dad's room.
- 那里吗 - 是的
- There? - Yeah.
我现在没那个闲工夫安慰你 所以
Look, I really don't have time to hold your hand here, so …
你什么意思
What are you saying?
你到客厅去等着吧
I'm saying go wait in the living room.
你爸爸也许不是每一件事
Your dad may not want you to know.
都想让你知道的
every single thing about him.
东西在哪
Where is it?
你是指我爸爸干的活儿的全部信息吗
You mean everything about the job my dad was working?
萨姆说你不知道的
Sam said you didn't know.
萨姆貌似很能干 于是我想 无所谓
Sam seemed competent, so I figured, fine …
我就按我爸爸一直说的那样做
I'll do what my dad always tells me to.
「做个普通的孩子 什么都别说
"Be a regular kid, don't say anything,
远离危险
stay out of the line of fire.
让大人去操心「
Let the adults work it out."
这条路算是行不通了
So much for that.
好吧
All right.
把东西给我
Hand it over.
行吗 我这个星期已经够烦的了
Okay? I have had a long, long week.
好吧 我懂了 你是个坚强的孩子
All right, I get it. You're a tough kid.
不过我是想把萨姆和你爸爸带回来
But I'm trying to get Sam and your dad back.
我爸爸离开了 没有回来
My dad left, and he didn't come back.
萨姆离开了 也没有回来
Sam left, and he didn't come back.
我把那些信息给你 你也会离开 不再回来
I give you the info, you leave, you don't come back.
我会回来的
I'm coming back.
我要跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
不不 才不要
N-no. No. Hell, no.
我要一起去
I'm coming!
否则你也别去了
Or you're not going.
现在把东西给我
Now hand it over.
给不了
I can't.
我都烧了
I burned it.
你什么了
You what?
不过算你走运 我烧之前都背了下来
But lucky for you, I memorized it all first.
我有个问题
Hey, I have a question.
好吧 规矩是这样的
All right, here's the deal.
我是个很幽默的人
I'm a fun guy.
我其实真的酷毙了
I'm actually awesome. Okay?
但现在 我没那种心情
But right now, I'm not in the mood.
我正考虑着正经事呢
I'm neck deep in some serious crap,
如果不是情况紧急
and if this wasn't an emergency,
我会把你扔到最近的商场去
I would drop your ass off at the nearest mall.
什么正经事
What serious crap?
报仇雪恨 行了吗
Revenge crap, all right?
现在给我闭嘴
Now shut up.
吃块饼干什么的
Eat a cookie or something.
可有件事讲不通
One thing doesn't make sense, though.
我爸爸是个很棒的猎人
My dad's a pretty great hunter,
你弟弟也壮得跟辆车似的 那么
and your brother's the size of a car, so…
那东西到底是怎么抓到他们俩的
so how'd this thing get 'em both?
嗜血鬼通常都是成对猎食的
Vetalas usually hunt in pairs.
萨姆和你爸爸都以为
Sam and your dad both assumed.
只有一个嗜血鬼独自猎食
it was one thing hunting solo.
他们怎么会这么想
Why'd they think that?
因为他们信息有误
Because they had the wrong info.
或者说 信息有限
Or, best available.
我们的爸爸多年前猎杀了一个不合群的
Our dad took down a loner years ago.
萨姆拿着他的日记
Sam has his journal.
你爸爸一定也是
Your dad must've been.
根据同样的「事实」做出判断的
going on the same facts.
那你是怎么知道实际情况的
And you know different 'cause…?
因为我几年前也猎杀过一个
Because I hunted one that turned out to be two.
后来才发现是两个
a couple years back.
而你却从来都没有告诉萨姆
And you never told Sam?
真是谢了
Wow, thanks.
何不把你的经验分享出来
How 'bout sharing that with the rest of the class.
我们才不会统统送命
so we don't all get killed?
萨姆当时去斯坦福念大学了 聪明蛋
Sam was away at Stanford, smartass.
萨姆上过大学
Sam went to college?
你不是说你们的爸爸是个猎人吗
I thought you said your dad was a hunter.
他的确是
He was.
我们都是
We were.
可萨姆退出 上了大学
Sam quit, went to college.
你也可以 上大学
You could, too, you know … go to college.
做个猎人兼儿科医师
Be a hunter/pediatrician.
今日特色菜 猎人 开怀畅饮吧
Hunter day at the all-you-can-eat.
大家感觉怎么样 还好吗
How's everyone feeling? Good?
闷不吭声啊 无所谓
Strong silent. Fine.
我也不用拿我的食物消遣
I don't need much entertainment with my meal.
萨莉 我跟你说过
Hey, Sally, uh, did I tell you.
我在犹他州猎杀的嗜血鬼吗
about the Vetalas I took down in Utah?
你让我想起了他们
You remind me of them.
不过他们要 年轻得多
Except they were so much…younger.
我把他们绑起来
I tied 'em up.
倒不是非绑不可
Not because I had to.
而是
More so…
我想慢慢来
I could take my time.
- 你在撒谎 - 没有
- You're lying. - No.
我不过是想让你知道
I just want you to know.
- 我多喜欢把你的姐妹们大卸八块的感觉 - 闭嘴
- how much I enjoyed cutting up your sisters. - Shut up!
你跟你爸爸一起干过活儿吗
You ever actually work with your dad?
当然
Sure. 'course.
不 我是指真正地参与
No, I mean work,
可不是在树林里射罐子
not shoot cans in the woods.
我一直都有帮忙
I mean, I help all the time.
也就是没有了
So, no.
你肚子现在
Well, right about now,
也差不多该饿了
your stomach should be pretty knotted up.
没有
Not really.
听着 可能你像我这么大的时候
Look, maybe this was a lot harder for you.
不能像我这么轻松应对
when you were my age.
你自认为是个好演员
Oh, you think you're a good actress.
但事实并非如此
You're not.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我真不想告诉你
Well, I hate to break it to you,
不过你满脸都写着 你很害怕
but it's all over your face … you're scared.
别再把我当成小女孩看待了
Quit treating me like I'm some girl.
我的一生都在为此做准备
I've been prepping for this my entire life.
训练是一回事
Training's one thing.
真正猎魔是完全不同的
Doing … whole nother beast.
你真的吓坏我了呢
Wow. You really scared me straight.
谢了 迪恩
Thanks, Dean.
那个女服务员为什么会进卡车里去
Why is that waitress getting into that truck?
我才不要跟你解释这种限制级的事
I'm not explaining the r-rated crap to you.
她坐进前面了 而不是后面 迪恩
The front of the truck, not the back, Dean.
不赖啊
All right.
这都什么年代了
What century is this?
早都没人再碰拳头了
No one fist-bumps anymore.
好了 别装了 你干得不错
Come on. Give it up. Good work.
你真是个老土
You're a dweeb.
- 你搞什么 - 我有个主意
- What the hell? - I got an idea.
不如你留在这儿吧
How 'bout you stay here?
你个混蛋
Oh, you jackass.
对 我是混蛋
Yeah, well, I'm the jackass.
但我可不会带个孩子去冒险 就这么定了
who ain't bringing a kid in there, period.
为什么
Why?
你能做到的我都能做到
I can do everything you can do.
我会把他们都救回来的 相信我
I'll bring them back. Trust me.
拜托 他们可能已经死了
Please, they're probably dead.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
都好几天了
It's been days.
可能只剩一滩肉了
Probably just a pile of meat.
我经历过的
I've seen it.
人是会死的 迪恩
People die, Dean.
我眼看着我妈妈被撕成碎片
I watched my mom get torn to shreds.
让我一起去 然后杀了她们
Let me go in there and kill them.
不行
No.
- 抱歉 - 你真是个伪君子
- Sorry. - You're such a hypocrite.
你为什么能去而我不行
How come you get to do it and I don't?
因为我是成年人
Because I'm the grown-up!
给我
Give it to me.
- 什么 你的撬锁工具
- What? - Your lock pick.
我会搜你身的
I will frisk you.
谢谢
Thank you.
幸好我们找到个新的
Good thing we picked up a new one.
这个快要喝干了
This one's about tapped out.
想跟我同时解决他俩吗
You want to finish him together?
没问题 很乐意
Sure. I'd love to.
别急啊
Not so fast.
爸爸 坚持下 我来救你
Dad, hold on. I got you!
克里希 不
Krissy, no!
放她走
Let her go…
否则我就让这个阳光小美女血溅当场
or little miss sunshine here gets it.
你怎么想的啊 把她带到这来
What were you thinking bring her here?
现在把刀放下
Now drop the knife!
她只是个孩子
She's just a child.
放她走
Let her go.
我想今天谁都走不了了
Yeah, I don't think we'll be letting anyone go.
爸爸
Daddy…
没事的 亲爱的
It's okay, baby.
不会出事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
好了 父女温情时刻结束了
All right. Enough with the family bonding.
是时候该让你闭嘴了
It's time for you to shut up.
爸爸 不
Daddy, no!
迪恩
Dean!
他帮不了你
He can't help you.
没人帮得了你
No one can.
那我就只能靠自己了
I guess I'll have to help myself, then.
演得烂 是吗
Bad actress, huh?
好吧 算我没说
Yeah, I take it back.
（急诊室）
我正在想你们什么时候过来呢
Yeah, I was hoping you'd stop by.
我想当面道声谢
I wanted to thank you.
不必客气
It's no problem.
你救了我的命 还有克里希的
No, you saved my life. Krissy's, too.
事实上 她救了我们所有人
Actually, uh she kind of saved ours.
别谢我们 退出吧
Don't thank us. Quit.
你女儿才十四岁
Your daughter's 14 years old.
她已经成为猎手 而且动手杀了一个怪物
She's already a hunter with a kill under her belt.
不是我多管闲事
I'm not trying to be a dick,
但你想想她以后的生活会怎么样
but what do you think that does to her life span?
她还有机会过上正常女孩的生活
She could still be a regular kid.
我入这行是有原因的
You know, I got into this for a reason.
我知道 是因为你的家人
I know. Your family.
你也应该为你现在的家人而退出这行
That's the same reason you should get out now.
我做不到
I can't.
你认识哪个猎人退出这一行了吗
You ever know anyone who left the life?
没有
No.
他们都在退出前被杀了
They all get killed first.
我们就不打扰了 你再休息会
Well, uh… we should probably let you get some rest.
好吧
Yeah.
迪恩
Dean!
谢谢你来道别 大笨蛋
Thanks for saying bye, asshat.
干吗 你不会是过来哭哭啼啼告别的吧
Oh, what? Now you're sentimental?
不是
No.
只是过来告诉你
Just wanted to tell you.
你这个老头挺有意思
that you're kind of amusing for an old man.
你是怎么打开手铐的
How'd you get out of them cuffs, anyway?
女孩都有自己的秘密
Girl's got to have her secrets.
发卡
Bobby pin.
你可能会送命的
You know, you could've gotten yourself killed.
我救了你的命
I saved your bacon.
我说的道理没错
My point stands,
但你确实救了我
but yes.
那么我想我就不干了
So… guess I'm retiring …
到此为止
one and done.
真的吗 你有什么感受吗
Really? How you feel about that?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
也许我会想萨姆一样 去斯坦福
Maybe I'll go to Stanford like Sam.
- 我们真逊 - 对 是的
- We're so lame. - Yeah, we are.
保重啊
Take care of yourself.
知道吗
You know what?
这样对他们也好
Good for them.
对
Yeah.
当你知道你的朋友已经没事时
It's nice to walk away from someone.
再离开 感觉真的很放心
and feel like they could be okay.
你怎么样 你没事吗
How about you? How you doing? You all right?
不 我肯定不是很好
No. I'm definitely not.
但也许…
But, you know, I mean, I think, maybe…
我只是想工作
I just want to work.
还用我问吗
Should I even ask?
我没事的
I'm fine.
「没事」的意思是…
"Fine, " meaning…?
你说得对 我们应该…
You're right. We should just…
专心工作 是不是
work, right?
然后想个辙干掉迪克·罗曼
And figure out a way to kick Dick Roman's ass.
我们可是专业人士
Well, hey, we are the professionals.